<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Testimonials on Geo Tattoos - Tattoo Making | Tattoo Removal | Tattoo Training | Tattoo Products</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/testimonials/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Testimonials on Geo Tattoos - Tattoo Making | Tattoo Removal | Tattoo Training | Tattoo Products</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 10:01:59 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/testimonials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Karthi Anu</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/testimonials/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 10:01:59 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/testimonials/4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am so much impressed with George’s work. It is Worth the cost spent! Looking forward for one more tattoo with you soon. I would strongly recommend this Geo Tattoos for all tattoo lovers. Very clean and hygienic. Keep up the good work and wish you grow more. My hearty wishes 😊&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Samantha Persis</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/testimonials/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 10:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/testimonials/5/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have took appointments regularly for tattoo removal from Mr. George himself and the results have been amazing. Continous checkup between each appointment and care guidance for cure is given after every seating. Neat and clean service is provided. Good ambience and Cost efficient as well. I would strongly recommend Geo Tattoo studio for tattoo removal and other tattoo services.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharad Rahmaniac</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/testimonials/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 10:01:52 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/testimonials/3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is my 3rd tattoo at geo tattoos. George sir is really awesome artist. His work is really superb. If I ever plan for new tattoos. It will be at Geo Tattoos.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nandhagopan</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/testimonials/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 10:01:46 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/testimonials/2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey, i&amp;rsquo;m really happy with your work Geo. Its really sexy shit. Love the way you upgraded a simple om with neat shading and all. Much appreciated, came out way better than I expected. Will certainly remember you because this is my first tattoo. I wish you all the best Geo. We might meet again!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rahul Richard</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/testimonials/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 10:01:35 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/testimonials/1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Excellent portrait of my Mother was done by George on 3rd April 2012. Really loved it and would come back again for more others who haven’t got a tattoo yet get one at geo tattoo. it’s really awesome!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
