<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>services on Geo Tattoos - Tattoo Making | Tattoo Removal | Tattoo Training | Tattoo Products</title>
    <link>https://www.geotattoos.com/tags/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in services on Geo Tattoos - Tattoo Making | Tattoo Removal | Tattoo Training | Tattoo Products</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 23:06:30 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.geotattoos.com/tags/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tattoo Making</title>
      <link>https://www.geotattoos.com/gallery/tattoo-making/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 23:06:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.geotattoos.com/gallery/tattoo-making/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;tattoo-making&#34;&gt;Tattoo Making&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A tattoo is a form of body modification where a design is made by inserting ink, dyes and pigments, either indelible or temporary, into the dermis layer of the skin to change the pigment. The process of tattooing involves the insertion of pigment into the skin&amp;rsquo;s dermis. Artists inject ink into a person&amp;rsquo;s skin to create tattoos. They use electrically powered tattoo machines
that resemble (and sound like) dental drills. Tattoo application uses mechanized needle to puncture the skin and inject ink into the dermis. Only 18 years plus can get tattoos. Tattoos are available for both exposed body and unexposed body.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tattoo Training</title>
      <link>https://www.geotattoos.com/gallery/tattoo-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 23:06:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.geotattoos.com/gallery/tattoo-training/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;tattoo-training&#34;&gt;Tattoo Training&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Geo Tattoos have created a training program that is widespread and designed to teach you to learn how to make tattoos with hands on experience. Because it&amp;rsquo;s an intensive training, which is designed to build character, stamina and focus you will be assisted in every aspect of the curriculum to make your training worth a lifetime. We have built the trust and our name in the
Tattoo Industry with all hard work and our unique style, so you can count on us to make you have a good brand as we have. George has trained more than 30 artists so far and has provided job and entrepreneurship for more than 15 artists. With his ability to serve the passionate people with his skills and patience has put him a step above of all professionals in the field. His attitude to contribute and teach his skills is remarkable. He is the perfect example for WIN-WIN&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tattoo Removal</title>
      <link>https://www.geotattoos.com/gallery/tattoo-removal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 23:06:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.geotattoos.com/gallery/tattoo-removal/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;tattoo-removal&#34;&gt;Tattoo Removal&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tattoo removal is most commonly performed using lasers that break down the ink particles in the tattoo. Tattoo removal has been performed with various tools since the start of tattooing. While tattoos were once considered permanent, it is now possible to remove them with treatments, fully or partially. Lasers remove tattoos by breaking up the pigment colors with a high-intensity light beam. Black tattoo pigment absorbs all laser wavelengths, making it the easiest color to treat. Other colors can only be treated by selected lasers based upon the pigment color. A tattoo removal process may take up to 6 months.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
